slutvidz.com 2017-11-30

# Privacy Policy

His document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on Dirtydirtyangels.com

The security of your Data is very important to Dirtydirtyangels.com and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.

This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority.

DATA COLLECTED

·        Personal Information: 

·        Non-Registered users can watch videos without registering and without any information being collected and processed. However the visitor's IP address will be recorded in the event that there is any misappropriation of information and/or content.

·        Registered Members: Registration is required for uploading videos, and accessing a number of other features. The following personal information is requested at the time of registration: username (required), and email address (required). Additional personal information, such as year of birth, relationship status and sexual orientation may be added on a voluntary basis after registration, for members interested in identifying and potentially contacting other members meeting specific criteria. All this data with the exception of the email address and IP address becomes publicly accessible information.

·        Content Uploaded to the site: Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.

·        Cookies: When you visit Dirtydirtyangels.com, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. Dirtydirtyangels.com uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site's features may not function properly.

·        Log File Information: When you visit Dirtydirtyangels.com, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.

·        Emails: If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.USES

·        Your personally identifiable information submitted to Dirtydirtyangels.com is used to provide to the user the website's features and special personalized features.

·        Your chosen username (not your email address) is displayed to other Users alongside the content you upload, including videos, comments, at, the messages you send through the Dirtydirtyangels.com private mail, etc. Other Users can contact you through, private messages.

·        Any videos that you submit to Dirtydirtyangels.com may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.

·        We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.

Dirtydirtyangels.com comply with all regulations of the data protections act of 1998. All data is stored in a secure location, whereby only specified individuals have access. In the event of data loss/leakage, Dirtydirtyangels.com have proceedures in places to try and secure this data, via several means. For information regarding these proceedures, and our compliance with the data protections act of 1998, please write to the legal team at LegalTeam@DirtyDirtyAngels.com.
